## 李文动 Wendong Li

Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications | +86 18677159530 | levscaut@bupt.edu.cn

#### **Personal Statement**

I'm an undergraduate student studying software engineering at Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications since 2019 and will be graduated in 2023. I have a solid foundation in math, programming, computer science and, deep learning. My research experience mainly focuses on artificial intelligence, including computer vision and graph neural network problems. I have interests in what I have studied before, and I'd like to try any other fields that associate with artificial intelligence or computer graphics.

## **Research Experience**

Research internship | National University of Singapore | Apr. 2022 - Present I am currently an intern research assistant at the NExT++ Centre, School of Computing, supervised by Prof. Tat-Seng Chua. My research projects focus on Knowledge Graph, in detail event forecasting, and few-shot learning. Our work is ready to submit to WSDM 2023 Demo and preparing the long paper for submitting to more conferences.

## Research internship | Tsinghua University | Aug. 2021 - Apr. 2022

I did a research internship at the Institute of HCI and Media Integration, Department of Computer Science and Technology, supervised by Prof. Yongjin Liu. My research projects focus on multimodal sketch-based computer vision problems, including image retrieval, image generation, and text co-conditioned image generation.

Research internship | Chinese Academy of Sciences | Apr. 2021 – Aug. 2021 | did a research internship at the Institute of Computing Technology supervised by Associate Research Fellow Di Zhao, studying introduction to AI, and exploring the acceleration of AI computing.

## **Project Experience**

#### Al Sheet Music Helper | Project in University's Innovation Competition

Following the idea of paper: MT3: Multi-Task Multitrack Music Transcription in ICLR 2022, we implement an auto music transcription system. By combining PyTorch with Flask as backend, and JavaScript as frontend, we elaborated an user-friendly web application for common instrument players. Even though they don't know about technology but they can still enjoy the convenience of AI.

#### Cross-Platform Chat App based on LibLinphone/Netty lib | Course Project

We implemented a chat app using one of two third-party libraries LibLinphone(using SIP as application layer protocol) and Netty as communication backend. We used Java for server and provided Android client and desktop client based on JavaFX.

#### Pneumonia Risk Status Platform for University | Course Project

Using React components and ECharts plugin, we provided a visualize platform for manager in the university to know about the current risk level of pneumonia in the campus. We used MyBatis to connect with MySQL and visualize the information in the database using simple statistic method and ECharts plugin.

#### Skill

C/C++/C#/Python/Java SE/EE

• English: TOEFL 102

Deep Learning

· School Band Drummer

#### **Education**

# Software Engineering | Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications | Sep. 2019 – Present

· Grade: 87/100

- Computer Science Courses: Computer Organization and Architecture, Operating System Principles, Computer Graphics, Algorithms and Data Structures, Compiling Theory, Computer Networks, Database Theory.
- Mathematical Courses: Advanced Mathematics, Linear Algebra, Discrete Mathematics,
  Possibility Theory, Numerical Analysis.